Okorafor Chidinma Christiana

Lagos, Nigeria | okoraforchidinma12@gmail.com | 08165381950

Profile

I have 3 years of experience as a customer service and technical support engineer for SKF bearings and M365 applications. I am competent in troubleshooting and resolving complex technical issues related to Office 365 products and bearings.

I also have a basic knowledge of HTML, CSS, and Javascript for front-end development. Additionally, I am familiar with version control systems like Git which ensures efficient and organized development of codes.

Education

B.Eng. Electronic Engineering - University of Nigeria, Nsukka	2014-2020
Certification Product Launches, Roadmapping, Strategy, Led-Growth, Analytics- Product School	2024
SKF Distributor College—SKF	2020-2023
Google Cloud – Coursera	2020
Fundamentals of Project Management—Coursera	2020
Fundamentals of Microsoft Office – New Horizon	2017

Technical Skills

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Git, React, Radix
- Microsoft Office 365, Exchange Online, SharePoint Online, OneDrive for Business, Teams, PowerShell, Active Directory, DNS
- · Agile and Scrum Methodologies
- ClickUp

Soft Skills

- Process Documentation
- Team Collaboration
- Self-driven to provide a timely solution
- Public Speaking
- Exceptional Verbal and Written Communication Skills

My Passion Project Link.

https://dymacode.github.io/learning-portfolio/

Work History

Product Manager- Regxta

12/2023-Present

- Directly managing 11 developers while addressing daily challenges to ensure product quality as well as accelerated issue resolution by 25%
- Crafted Product Requirement Document to scope and manage the launch of the Regxta version 2.0 within the 1st Quarter.
- I Handle data and user feedback to improve product features, resulting in a 4% increase in Netprofit.
- I create user stories, and tickets on click-up and assign these tasks to the required development team.

Technical Support Engineer- Tek Experts Nigeria

07/2023-12/2023

- I Provided technical support to clients via phone and email resolving issues promptly and ensuring customer satisfaction.
- Diagnosed software problems, and troubleshoot technical issues related to Microsoft 365 applications that use these products in the NOAM region(USA, Canada).
- I collaborated with the development team to escalate and resolve complex technical issues, contributing to product improvement.
- I documented support processes and created knowledge base articles for common issues, reducing resolution time.

Customer Service – FirstAdvancetek Solutions Limited, Lagos

09/2020-06/2023

- I provided Technical Support for SKF bearings, lubricants, maintenance tools, etc. to customers to keep customers satisfied.
- Processed documentation for tracking the progress of SKF products and completed 93% on-time delivery.
- I conducted initial Product analysis for companies to determine their needs.
- I Developed lasting customer relationships through promos and discounts for loyalty.
- Implemented product changes and recommendations for customers.

Information Technology Intern – Alpha Mead Group, Lagos

06/2017 - 11/2017

• I installed and configured computer hardware, software, systems, networks, printers, and scanners and set up accounts for new users.

- I provided end-to-end technical support for M365 applications and services, including Exchange Online, SharePoint Online, OneDrive for Business, and Teams.
- Troubleshoot and resolve complex technical issues related to M365 services, including user management, email routing, calendar sharing, site collection configuration, and data loss prevention.
- I Collaborated with team members to deliver technical solutions and training materials to staff on using the Softphone.
- I administered and configured M365 environments, including user management, licensing, security, and compliance.
- Provided technical support across the company to resolve technical issues and improve M365 service delivery (in person or over the phone).
- Documented inquiries and solutions are taken in resolving technical issues.